{
    "data": [
        {
            "ID": "DlXFaesGBpoF",
            "Question": "Thanks, {{answer_60906475}}! What's it like where you live? Tell us in a few sentences.",
            "Answer": "It's cold right now! I live in an older medium-sized city with a university. Geographically, the area is hilly."
        },
        {
            "ID": "SMEUb7VJz92Q",
            "Question": "If you're OK with our city management following up if they have further questions, please give us your email address.",
            "Answer": "laura@example.com"
        },
        {
            "ID": "JwWggjAKtOkA",
            "Question": "What is your first name?",
            "Answer": "Laura"
        },
        {
            "ID": "KoJxDM3c6x8h",
            "Question": "When did you move to the place where you live?",
            "Answer": "2005-10-15"
        },
        {
            "ID": "PNe8ZKBK8C2Q",
            "Question": "Which pictures do you like? You can choose as many as you like.",
            "Answer": [
                "London",
                "Sydney"
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": "Q7M2XAwY04dW",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the weather in Sydney? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather",
            "Answer": 5
        },
        {
            "ID": "gFFf3xAkJKsr",
            "Question": "By submitting this form, you understand and accept that we will share your answers with city management. Your answers will be anonymous will not be shared.",
            "Answer": true
        },
        {
            "ID": "k6TP9oLGgHjl",
            "Question": "Which of these cities is your favorite?",
            "Answer": {
                "label": "London"
            }
        },
        {
            "ID": "RUqkXSeXBXSd",
            "Question": "Do you have a favorite city we haven't listed?",
            "Answer": false
        },
        {
            "ID": "NRsxU591jIW9",
            "Question": "How important is the weather to your opinion about a city? 1 is not important, 5 is very important.",
            "Answer": 2
        },
        {
            "ID": "WOTdC00F8A3h",
            "Question": "How would you rate the weather where you currently live? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather.",
            "Answer": 3
        },
        {
            "ID": "pn48RmPazVdM",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the general quality of life in Sydney? 1 is poor, 5 is excellent",
            "Answer": 4
        },
        {
            "ID": "DlXFaesGBpoF",
            "Question": "Thanks, {{answer_60906475}}! What's it like where you live? Tell us in a few sentences.",
            "Answer": "It's cold right now! I live in an older medium-sized city with a university. Geographically, the area is hilly."
        },
        {
            "ID": "SMEUb7VJz92Q",
            "Question": "If you're OK with our city management following up if they have further questions, please give us your email address.",
            "Answer": "laura@example.com"
        },
        {
            "ID": "JwWggjAKtOkA",
            "Question": "What is your first name?",
            "Answer": "Laura"
        },
        {
            "ID": "KoJxDM3c6x8h",
            "Question": "When did you move to the place where you live?",
            "Answer": "2005-10-15"
        },
        {
            "ID": "PNe8ZKBK8C2Q",
            "Question": "Which pictures do you like? You can choose as many as you like.",
            "Answer": [
                "London",
                "Sydney"
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": "Q7M2XAwY04dW",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the weather in Sydney? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather",
            "Answer": 5
        },
        {
            "ID": "gFFf3xAkJKsr",
            "Question": "By submitting this form, you understand and accept that we will share your answers with city management. Your answers will be anonymous will not be shared.",
            "Answer": true
        },
        {
            "ID": "k6TP9oLGgHjl",
            "Question": "Which of these cities is your favorite?",
            "Answer": {
                "label": "London"
            }
        },
        {
            "ID": "RUqkXSeXBXSd",
            "Question": "Do you have a favorite city we haven't listed?",
            "Answer": false
        },
        {
            "ID": "NRsxU591jIW9",
            "Question": "How important is the weather to your opinion about a city? 1 is not important, 5 is very important.",
            "Answer": 2
        },
        {
            "ID": "WOTdC00F8A3h",
            "Question": "How would you rate the weather where you currently live? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather.",
            "Answer": 3
        },
        {
            "ID": "pn48RmPazVdM",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the general quality of life in Sydney? 1 is poor, 5 is excellent",
            "Answer": 4
        },
        {
            "ID": "DlXFaesGBpoF",
            "Question": "Thanks, {{answer_60906475}}! What's it like where you live? Tell us in a few sentences.",
            "Answer": "It's cold right now! I live in an older medium-sized city with a university. Geographically, the area is hilly."
        },
        {
            "ID": "SMEUb7VJz92Q",
            "Question": "If you're OK with our city management following up if they have further questions, please give us your email address.",
            "Answer": "laura@example.com"
        },
        {
            "ID": "JwWggjAKtOkA",
            "Question": "What is your first name?",
            "Answer": "Laura"
        },
        {
            "ID": "KoJxDM3c6x8h",
            "Question": "When did you move to the place where you live?",
            "Answer": "2005-10-15"
        },
        {
            "ID": "PNe8ZKBK8C2Q",
            "Question": "Which pictures do you like? You can choose as many as you like.",
            "Answer": [
                "London",
                "Sydney"
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": "Q7M2XAwY04dW",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the weather in Sydney? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather",
            "Answer": 5
        },
        {
            "ID": "gFFf3xAkJKsr",
            "Question": "By submitting this form, you understand and accept that we will share your answers with city management. Your answers will be anonymous will not be shared.",
            "Answer": true
        },
        {
            "ID": "k6TP9oLGgHjl",
            "Question": "Which of these cities is your favorite?",
            "Answer": {
                "label": "London"
            }
        },
        {
            "ID": "RUqkXSeXBXSd",
            "Question": "Do you have a favorite city we haven't listed?",
            "Answer": false
        },
        {
            "ID": "NRsxU591jIW9",
            "Question": "How important is the weather to your opinion about a city? 1 is not important, 5 is very important.",
            "Answer": 2
        },
        {
            "ID": "WOTdC00F8A3h",
            "Question": "How would you rate the weather where you currently live? 1 is poor weather, 5 is excellent weather.",
            "Answer": 3
        },
        {
            "ID": "pn48RmPazVdM",
            "Question": "On a scale of 1 to 5, what rating would you give the general quality of life in Sydney? 1 is poor, 5 is excellent",
            "Answer": 4
        }
    ]
}